A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1974-2006.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction (Accession 39607), 1974-2006., Extent: xx boxes. (Box 1-xx)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1981-1982.
    - Speeches: Virginia Association of Elementary School Principals, 1982 Apr 22. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Commencement Address - Clover Hill High School, Chesterfield, 1982 June 10. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Comments at the retirement of Dr. Melton F. Wright, 1982 June 12. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Standards of Learning Workshop, 1982 June 21. (Box 16)
    - Speeches: Secondary School Principals Conference, 1982 June 23-25. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Dr. S. John Davis (miscellaneous), 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: From Dr. S. John Davis, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Administrative Director for Board/Staff Relations - Maggie S. Nelson, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Cochran, William H., 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Cochran, William H. - Meetings, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Cochran, William - Committees and Councils, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Cochran - Indirect costs, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Cochran - Title I Audit Hearing, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Cochran /Price, Dr. James - Block Grants, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Cochran - Stop Drugs at the Source, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Administrative Review Director - S. Barry Morris, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Associate Director of Federal Programs - Mr. Wildy, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Program Development - Dr. R. L. Boyer, 1981-1982. (Box 16)
    - Correspondence: Management Information Services - Mr. Howell Gruver, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Research, Evaluation and Testing - Dr. Gerald Bracey, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Research, Evaluation and Testing - Pilot studies/Title IV-C, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Administrative Field Services - Dr. E.B. Howerton, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Personnel - Mr. Waitman, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Personnel - Organization of Dept. of Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Professional development, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Community Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Teacher Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Teacher Education - Certification Workshop, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Technical Assistant - Dr. V.W. Hylton, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Assistant Superintendent for Curriculum and Instruction, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Callie Shingleton, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Standards of Learning Objectives, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Division of Sciences and Elementary Administration, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Driver Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Health and Physical Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Mathematics Service, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Science Service, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Human and Secondary Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: English / Language Arts Service, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: History, Government and Geography, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Foreign Languages, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Music Service, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Dr. N. Grant Tubbs, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Special Education - Mr. James Micklem, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Career Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Gifted and Talented, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Bureau of Teaching Materials, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: AVS Letters of support, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Guidance Service, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: School Libraries and Textbooks, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Telecommunications, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Director Title I - Mr. Conyers, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Migrant Education - Mr. Irby, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Melvin Garner, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Adult Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Agricultural Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Distributive Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Home Economic Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Industrial Arts, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Proprietary Schools, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Veterans training, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Administration and Finance - Mr. M.E. Cale (4 folders), 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Director of Finance - Mr. T.J. Bise, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Director of Finance - Budget (1982-1984), 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Administrative Support Service, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Basic School Aid - Mr. Hager, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Pupil Transportation - Mr. R.A. Bynum, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: School Buildings - Mr. John Hamill, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: School Food Service - Mr. John Miller, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Public Information - Harry L. Smith, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Personnel newsletter, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
    - Correspondence: Radford Office - Dept. of Education, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1982-1983.
    - A - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - American Association of School Administrators, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Appalachian Educational Laboratory, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Accomack County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Albemarle County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Alexandria, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Alleghany County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Amelia County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Appomattox County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Arlington County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Augusta County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - B - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Blood Drive, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Bath County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Bedford County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Bland County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Botetourt County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Bristol, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Brunswick County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Buchanan County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Buckingham County, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Buena Vista, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - C - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Centex Center for Excellence, Inc., 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - CETA informational materials, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Christmas party, 1982. (Box 19a)
    - Colleges and Universities - Virginia (folder 1), 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Colleges and Universities - Virginia (folder 2), 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Colleges and Universities - Out of state, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Community Colleges, 1982-1983. (Box 19a)
    - Campbell County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Cape Charles, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Carroll County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Charles City County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Charlotte County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Chesapeake, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Chesterfield County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Clarke County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Colonial Heights, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Covington, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Craig County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Craig County - Literary Fund, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Culpeper County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Cumberland County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - D - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Developmental Disabilities Protection and Advocacy Office, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Developmental Disabilities Planning Council, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Danville, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Dickenson County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Dinwiddie County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - E - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Education Commission of the States, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Equal Employment Opportunities Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - F - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Fairfax City, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Fairfax County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Falls Church, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Fauquier County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Floyd County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Frederick County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Fredericksburg, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Fries, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - G - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - General Assembly - House of Delegates, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - General Assembly - Senate, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - General Assembly - Fiscal impact statements, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Governor's Commission on Virginia's Future, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Commission, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Galax, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Giles County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Goochland County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Grayson County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - Greene County, 1982-1983. (Box 19b)
    - H - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Halifax County / South Boston, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Hampton, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Harrisonburg, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Henrico County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Highland County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Hopewell, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - I - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Impact aid (folder 1), 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Impact aid (folder 2), 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Isle of Wight County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - J - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Japan, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Jobs for Virginia graduates, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Juvenile Delinquency Advisory Council, Governor's, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - James City County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - K - Correspodnence, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Keep America Beautiful, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - King and Queen County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - King George County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - King William County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - King William County - Educating Indian children, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - L - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Lancaster County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Lee County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Lexington, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Loudoun County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Louisa County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Lunenburg County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Lynchburg, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - M - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - MS Read-a-thon Advisory Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Marsh and McLennan, Inc. (Liability insurance), 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Madison County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Manassas, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Manassas Park, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Martinsville, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Mathews County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Middlesex County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - Montgomery County, 1982-1983. (Box 20a)
    - N - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education - Southern Regional Conference, 1983. (Box 20b)
    - National Commission on Excellence in Education, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - National Education Association, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - National Institute of Education, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Nelson County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Newport News, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Norfolk, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Northampton County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Northumberland County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Nottoway County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - O - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - On Board, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Orange County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - P - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Peninsula Area Cooperative Educational Services, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Personnel Newsletter (VDOE), 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Presidential Scholars' Honors Ceremony - U.S. Dept. of Education, Region III, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Procurement Act, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Patrick County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Poquoson, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Portsmouth, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Powhatan County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Prince Edward County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Prince George County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Prince William County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Pulaski County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Q- Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - R - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Register of Regulations, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Radford, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Richmond City, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Richmond County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Roanoke City, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Roanoke County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Rockbridge County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Rockingham County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - Russell County, 1982-1983. (Box 20b)
    - S - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Six Year Plan Objective, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Southeastern Cooperative Education Programs, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Southeastern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Standards of Learning Objectives - National Commission on Excellence in Education Report, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - State Advocacy Office for the Developmentally Disabled, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - State Departments of Education - Other states, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - State-Ed, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - State Employees Credit Union, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - State Special Education Advisory Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Superintendent's Advisory Council, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Superintendent's Employee Advisory Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Superintendents Study Group, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Shenandoah County, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Smyth County, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Southampton County, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Stafford County, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Staunton, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Suffolk, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Surry County, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - T - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - Tazewell County, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - United Way Campaign, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U.S. Congress, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education - Office for Civil Rights, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education - Office of Special Education, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U.S. Secretary of Education, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Justice - Land and Natural Resources Division, Office of the Attorney General (Asbestos Liability), 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - U.S. Savings Bond Campaign, 1982-1983. (Box 21a)
    - V - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Association for Children with Learning Disabilities, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Association for Education of the Gifted, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Association of Elementary School Principals, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Association of School Administrators, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Association of Secondary School Principals, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Association of Independent Schools, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Association of Independent Special Education Facilities, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Community College System, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care, Inc., 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Developmental Disabilities Planning Council, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Education Association, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Forum on Education, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia High School League, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia High School League - Meeting, 1983 Jan. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Public School Authority, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Register Committee / Register of Regulations, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Schools for the Deaf, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia State Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce - Education Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia State Library, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Taxpayers Association, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Vocational-Technical and Career Education - Joint Subcommittee, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Virginia Beach, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - W - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Warren County, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Washington County, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - West Point, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Westmoreland County, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Williamsburg, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Winchester, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Wise County, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Wythe County, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - Y - Correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - York County, 1982-1983. (Box 21b)
    - State Government: Dept. of Agriculture, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Appropriations Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Attorney General (1), 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Attorney General (2), 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Attorney General - Cases, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Attorney General - Civil Digest, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Children, Division of, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Comptroller's Office, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Computer Services, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Corrections, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Council of Higher Education, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: General Services, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Emergency and Energy Services, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Governor's Conference on Reevaluating the Fundamentals of State Government, 1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Governor Robb - Schools, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Copies forwarded of correspondence from the Governor, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Executive orders, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Miscellaneous, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Virginia Liaison Office, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Governor's Education Advisory Committee - Block grants, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Lieutenant Governor, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1982-1983. (Box 22a)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education (1), 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education (2), 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education (3), 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Human Affairs, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Transportation, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: health Dept., 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Highways Dept., 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Legislative Automated Systems, Division of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Legislative Services, Div. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Miscellaneous State Agencies, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Rehabilitative School Authority, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: State Agency Group Luncheon, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Telecommunications, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Transportation Safety, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Treasurer, State, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Govenor's Advisory Committee on Child Abuse and Neglect, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Governor's Plan and Substance Abuse, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - State Government: Governor's Employment and Training Council, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - The Shaping of Public Policy: Understanding the System and Making It Work for Children and You, 1982-1983. (Box 22b)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1982. (Box 23a)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1983. (Box 23a)
    - Boyer, R. L., 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Bracey, Gerald, 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Bracey, Gerald, 1983. (Box 23a)
    - Cochran, William H., 1982 July-Aug. (Box 23a)
    - Cochran, William H., 1982 Sept-Oct. (Box 23a)
    - Cochran, William H., 1982 Nov-Dec. (Box 23a)
    - Cochran, William H., 1983. (Box 23a)
    - Gruver, Howell L., 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Howerton, Everett B., Jr., 1982. (Box 23a)
    - Howerton, Everett B., Jr., 1983. (Box 23a)
    - Lovern, Mary, 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Morris, S. Barry, 1982. (Box 23a)
    - Morris, S. Barry, 1983. (Box 23a)
    - Sale, Donald S., 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Waitman, H. Nick, 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Wildy, Vernon L., 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Accreditation, 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Accreditation - Associations, 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Accreditation - Cities, 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Accreditation - Counties, 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Accreditation - Presentations, 1982-1983. (Box 23a)
    - Governor's Task Force to Combat Drunk Driving, 1982-1983. (Box 23b)
    - Governor's Task Force on Science and Technology, 1982-1983. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis), 1982-1983. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Virginia Valley Migrant Education Workshop, 1982 Aug. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Dedication of North Stafford High School, 1982 Nov. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Dedication of Richmond County Elementary School, 1982 Nov. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Dedication of Council Elementary School, Buchanan Co., 1982 Dec. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Teachers meeting, Buchanan Co., 1982 Dec. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Virginia Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development, 1982 Dec. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Proprietary Schools Conference, 1982 Dec. (Box 23b)